SERGEI ANDREEV

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Novi Sad, Serbia

PHONE

+381 611399396

EMAIL

s.andreev.it@gmail.com

TELEGRAM

@and1tmn

LINKEDIN

linkedin.com/in/s-andreev-it/

SUMMARY

As a skilled front-end developer with 4+ years of experience, I've had the opportunity to work on a diverse range of complex projects and utilize various technologies. One of my greatest strengths is working effectively in distributed, diverse international teams.

SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, Material UI
- JavaScript, TypeScript
- React, Redux, NextJS, Axios
- NodeJS
- Git, Docker, Webpack

EDUCATION

Industrial University of Tyumen

2015-2019

Computer systems and complexes

LANGUAGE

English - B2 Russian - Native

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend developer

Dualboot partners

Product Design & Software Engineering Company

06/2021- Present (1 year 11 months)

- Developed the client side of applications and admin panels using React, Redux, Redux-toolkit, Redux-thunk, TypeScript, NextJS, Axios and Material UI;
- Developed a desktop application for online proctoring using Electron, React, and NodeJS;
- Actively communicated with clients to clarify requirements, prioritize and demonstrate releases;
- Suggested technical solutions and ideas through design review and analysis, peer programming, and code review.

Frontend developer

Tenzor

Large Holding Engaged in Software Development 12/2019- 06/2021 (1 year 6 months)

- Developed new features, fixed bugs, and implemented enhancements to improve the functionality and speed of the web platform using TypeScript and Less;
- Supported and debugged the legacy code on the frontend side;
- Communicated with colleagues from other departments and reviewed colleagues' code.

Frontend developer

Unidom

Real Estate Agency

02/2019-12/2019 (10 months)

- Developed the layout of the corporate website using HTML, SCSS, JavaScript;
- Developed the client part of a multi-page corporate website from Figma.